# GRANT GLOMSTEAD

7050 Hatchery Rd, Waterford MI, 48327 gglomstead@comcast.net (248)-410-9059

### Objective

Having recently graduated with a master's in engineering technology from Wayne State University, I plan on obtaining a long, successful career in the Audio/Visual/Broadcast engineering field. Along with years of experience in IT, and a bachelor's degree from Michigan State, I plan to use my skills to succeed in the AV-tech industry.

### Education

Wayne State University Graduated in May 2019.

42 W Warren Ave, Detroit, MI 48202 Master's in Engineering Technology.

Michigan State University Graduated in June 2017.

East Lansing, Michigan 48824 Major: B.S. in Media and Information.

Minor: Information and Technology.

## **Work Experience**

#### TV Studio Intern at Independence Television

07/2019 - Present

Duties: Audio-Video production including live events and remote shoots. Experience with a multitude of AV systems such as multicasters, switchers, and more. Supervisor – Matt Bleau: 248-623-3661.

#### System Support Specialist at Marsh and McLennan Agency

03/2018 - Present

Duties: Imaging computers, managing servers, working in active directory, and general computer maintenance. Supervisor – AJ Michaud: 989-355-0145.

#### System Administrator/Video Producer at Line2Line Coatings

06/2011 - Present

Duties: Promotional video production, and system administration. Performed system security, server installation, video surveillance and more. Supervisor - Andy Suman: 248-310-1850.

### **Technician Assistant at CAS Technology Department at MSU**

04/2015 - 08/2017

Duties: Installing, maintaining, and fixing a wide array of computers/AV Tech in the Communication, Arts, Sciences building at Michigan State University. Supervisor – Sam Mills: 517-490-1179.

### Internship at DMC Huron Valley Sinai Hospital

05/2012 - 06/2012

Duties: Internship with the Information-Technology Department and other departments such as: Marketing, Operating Room, Cath Lab, Facilities, and more. Supervisor - Deana Brightman.

# **Skills Summary**

- Please feel free to browse my portfolio at: <a href="https://glomstea.github.io/">https://glomstea.github.io/</a>
- Knowledge and experience with web-based languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and SQL, plus
  other languages such as C++, PLC, Atmel AVR, and Python as well as a Certificate for the Fanuc Handling
  Tool Operations, Robot Programming and ROBOGUIDE Simulation Course.
- Skills dealing with implementation, maintenance, and problem solving on all computer operating systems.
- Experience with video/audio production and graphic design as well as Adobe Creative Suite.
- Hands on experience with Extron, Textron, and other AV components while working on projects such as the new Spartan Newsroom and Immersive Media/Motion Capture Studio at MSU.